digicamdb.com 2017-08-09

# Privacy policy

### Privacy policy for digicamdb.com

**Short version:**

This website (digicamdb.com) does not collect any personally identifiable information. And rest assured that information voluntarily supplied by users will not be sold, shared or redistributed to any third party. 

**Long version:**

## Collected Information

This website collects only non-personally-identifying information - standard server logs which include information such as internet protocol (IP) address, type of browser, operating system used, internet service provider (ISP), referring, exit and visited pages, date/time stamp, etc. This information is used for statistical purposes and to provide the best user experience to the visitors. 

I do not request or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. 

## Contact Form

If you volunteer to submit your personal information via contact form or email, the information will be used solely to contact you back in order to reply to your email. 

As stated before, your personal information will not be sold, shared or redistributed to any third party. I will not use this information for any purpose other than its intended use. 

## Cookies

This site does not require cookies and does not use cookies to collect personal information. 

## External Links

There are links to other websites on this site. These other websites are not managed or controlled by me and are not covered by this privacy policy. When you follow a link to another site, you are subject to the privacy policy of that site. I'm not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such third party websites. 

## Third Party Ads

Please note that this site serves ads from third parties (such as Google) and third-party ad servers may use cookies to serve ads. Google, for example, uses the DART cookie. You should note that I have no access to or control over cookies used by third-party advertisers. To learn more about the DART cookie you may visit the Google ads privacy policy at [google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/)

## Conclusion

By visiting and using digicamdb.com you automatically agree to this privacy policy. I reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time. Any changes will be posted on this page. 

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, you can contact me [here](http://www.digicamdb.com/contact/). 

Gregor B. 

Last updated: **May 23, 2016**
